Hi!
I'm Huang Ziling
In this project I work as a full stack developer.
I started by designing ui and ux in figma.
I've created
detailed frames to give our found and a clear guide. Moving to the backend.
I set up the RDS database to store all the apps data.
After that I built the flask APIs for whether.
And journey planning using google maps geocoding.
Most importantly,
I also build a data pipeline for our machine learning model.
For the front end,
I created interactive journey planning maps and a reusable weather widget.
I also created a complete chat page.
Finally,
to make sure everything works well,
I wrote unit test for my APIs.
Besides serving as a scrum master for sprint 2,
I also authored the architecture and design section of our final report.